a successful project Demands a compact
strategy aligned with user needs what if
you can stay on the same page understand
their needs and complete a cracking
project introducing Flint road map a
game-changing add-on and a huge step
towards making fluent boards a complete
project management solution fluent road
map is a visual tool that breaches the
project management process with your
client's requirements bringing Clarity
and accountability to your workflow as a
comes with FBS Pro you need nothing
extra to manage it separately simply
install flnro map and you're are good to
get started just the way you create a
new board click add board then provide a
title and description the magic box to
convert your board into road map awaits
right below take the box and it will ask
you to Define
stages once you deal with the stages
save it to take off with FL road map
Fint road map offers the same
customization options as Flyn boards
with an interesting feature to watch out
for easily decide which stages to show
publicly and which to keep behind the
scenes it's super easy with the make
this stage admin only button in the
settings that's not all just select the
I button and the word information with
the description will appear from there
you can readily select a page to
Showcase your road map or copy and paste
the link to any page you want once you
are up with Flint road map your
customers can share their views which
will be added Direct directly to the
back end and the upvot feature will
never fail you to understand your
client's needs with a crystal clear idea
of your top priorities everyone's now on
the same page with a bird's eye view
thanks to Flint road map for making it
happen so keep your clients aligned with
your plan develop a better product
together and unlock long-term success
with a simple yet effective solution
fluent road map don't wait grab it now